<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Zichen Chen</title><link>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/</link><description>Recent content on Zichen Chen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 01:46:58 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/about/</guid><description>Selected Awards and Honors UCSB Fellowship, UCSB, USA
Nomination, IJCAI 2020 AI Video Competition, Japan
Outstanding Chinese Students Scholarship (x6), CYCU, Taiwan
Honorary Membership, The Phi Tau Phi Scholastic Honor Society
Membership, Gamma Sigma Academic Honor Society
Education 2021-now, PhD in Computer Science, UCSB, USA
2017-2020, M.Eng (Research) in Computer Science and Engineering, NTU, Singapore
2013-2017, B.B.A in Information System, CYCU, Taiwan (GPA: 3.96/4.0 (1/118))</description></item><item><title>Service</title><link>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 01:46:49 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/service/</guid><description>Conference PC Member FL-AAAI 2022, FL-IJCAI 2021, FL-ICML 2021, FL-IJCAI 2020
Journal Reviewer IEEE Intelligent Systems</description></item><item><title>Pub</title><link>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/pub/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 01:46:41 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/pub/</guid><description>Book Chapter Zichen Chen, Zelei Liu, Kang Loon Ng, Han Yu, Yang Liu and Qiang Yang, “A Gamified Research Tool forIncentive Mechanism Design in Federated Learning”, Federated Learning: Privacy and Incentive, 2020
Conference Zichen Chen, Yuanyuan Chen, Han Yu, “Federated Block Dropout for Efficient Federated Learning with Large-Scale Models”, IJCAI, 2022 (pending submit)
Yuanchao Loh, Zichen Chen, Yansong Zhao, Han Yu, “A Simulation Platform for Studying Attacks on Federated Learning”, IJCAI, 2022 (pending submit)</description></item><item><title>Proj</title><link>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/proj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 01:46:31 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://chen-zichen.github.io/index/proj/</guid><description>Federated Learning Topics include: secure cmmunication optimization, Singapore COVID-19 contact tracing, incentive mechanism design, trust-based learning.
Recommender System Had a research intern in Alibaba, working on transfer learning, cross-domain recommendation, and federated recommendation.
Cooperative Reinforcement Learning Working on multi-agent reinforcement learning and space segmentation for search-and-rescue operation.</description></item></channel></rss>